(Sheldon:)Um...
(Sheldon:)In a hundred years, you'll both
be dead and it won't matter?
No! Come on! You're supposed to say,
"Of course he misses you.
(Penny:)The only reason he's partying
is to cover up his pain."
(Sheldon:)Oh, no, I don't think
that's true at all.
(Penny:)This is ridiculous.
(Penny:)Why am I upset just because
he's off having a good time?
(Sheldon:)Well, perhaps you're
obsessively picturing him
(Sheldon:)engaged in drunken coitus
with another woman.
(Sheldon:)Is that it?
Did I get it right?
Okay, that's great. You can stop
trying to make me feel better now.
(Sheldon:)Actually, I can't.
(Sheldon:)Before Leonard left, he made me
promise that I'd take care of you.
(Penny:)-He did?
-Yes.
Oh! That's really sweet.
(Sheldon:)Plus, if I do a good job, he said
he'd bring me back a sailor's cap.